Yahoo.
やっほー
How have you been?
元気してた?
Yes, I did.
うん、してた
lie?
うそ?
Let's take it easy for a while.
ちょっと、ゆっくりしよう
Yeah, okay.
うん、いいよ
So cute.
可愛いな
It's not cute.
可愛くない
可愛くないくないよ
Yahoo.
やっほー
It was so cute that I ended up touching it all the time.
可愛 すぎてまずいと触りっぱなっちゃった
That's amazing.
すげーすげーじゃん
What's going on?
どうなってんの?
Check how you're doing.
調子を見してよ
Look, it's cute.
ほら、可愛い
Disney character?
ディズニーのキャラ?
Are you conscious?
意識してんの?
this.
これ
What's going on?
ちょっとどうなってんの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
Stick your butt out a little.
ちょっとお尻突き出しして
You look like an adult with your pants open.
成人そうなパンツ開いてんね
Sugo
すーご
stomach.
い
Wow, she's wearing cute clothes.
すごい 可愛い服着てる
I have truly become an adult.
まさに大人になってきちゃった
Please take a good look at it.
しっかり見してあげて
Shift it a little.
ちょっとずらしてろ
I'll say it.
言いちゃうよ
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Don't worry about it.
気にしないでほら
Tulle.
チュールして
You won't be embarrassed if you do this.
こうしたら恥ずかしくないでしょ
Two.
2つ
It's not coming from your nose.
鼻からくないでしょ
a bit.
少し
I feel like it's a little closed.
ちょっと閉めてる気がする
Is it just my imagination?
気のせいかな?
気のせい?
stomach
い
Make that sound.
っち の音して
Is it just my imagination?
気のせい?
Look at the front.
正面を見てほら
By the way, look at your pants.
ちなみにさ、 じゃあパンツ見て
Look at your pants.
パンツ見て
why?
なんで?
Why look?
なんでほら?
Look at my pants.
私のパンツ見て
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
what?
何?
I want you to sleep.
寝てほしい
Won't you touch me?
触ってあげない?
You don't like it, do you?
嫌でしょ
You want me to touch you, right?
触ってほしいでしょ?
Look at my pants.
パンツ見てって
what?
何?
It's not embarrassing, is it?
恥ずかしくないでしょ
You wouldn't be embarrassed if you wore tulle.
チュールしてたら恥ずかしくないでしょ
I feel like it's closing down more and more.
どんどん閉めてきてる気が
do.
する
Well, let's attack.
さ あ、攻めてあげようか
Well, you like chestnuts.
あれ、くりぃ好きなのね
Is it just my imagination?
気のせいかな?
I think I brought Zako-kun.
ザコくん持ってきた気がする
It sounds a little unpleasant.
ちょっと嫌らしい音する
Can you hear me?
聞こえるかな?
You're not embarrassed because you're wearing clothes.
服着てるから恥ずかしくないでしょ
I won't touch you here.
触ってあげないよ、ここ
What is this?
これ何?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Why don't you like it?
なんで嫌だ?
You're not embarrassed because you're wearing clothes.
服着てるから恥ずかしくないでしょ
But I want you to touch it.
でも触ってほしい
what?
何?
It went up a lot.
めちゃくちゃ上がってきちゃった
Okay.
いいよ
I'm starting to feel really good.
すごく気持ちよくなってきた
I can't do it anymore.
もう無理だ
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
Let's go now.
もう行こう
No way, no way.
無理無理
I really can't stand it.
本当に我慢できない
what?
何?
What are you doing?
何 して ん の?
何してんの?
What are you doing?
何 して んの?
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いね
It's cute.
可愛いね
I'm thinking of trying various things.
色々しようと思って
It's no good anymore.
もうダメだよ
It's downtown.
ダウンタウン中だろ
now?
今は?
No.
ダ メ
Because it happened last time.
前回あるんだから
This girl is a JK.
JKだよ、この子
Are you a JK?
JKですか?
I'll start it.
俺が始まるんだよ
What were you thinking just now?
お前、今思ってたのかよ
It's cute.
可愛いね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's cute.
可愛いね
It's been a while.
久しぶりだね
Like this.
こんな
What's the bottom like?
下 がどんなの?
amazing.
すごい
Behind, behind.
後ろ、後ろ
I was shaking my ass.
お尻フリフリしたよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
cute.
可愛い
I don't like it.
嫌だ
amazing.
すごい
water
水
I want to wear it.
着 みたい
delicious?
美味しい?
It tastes like milk.
ミルクの味がする
difficult.
難しい
cute.
可愛 い
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だ
It's a red butt.
赤いお尻だね
It's so delicious.
すっごい美味しい
It's mango.
マンゴーしてるね
Look.
ほら
Nice to meet you, Mango.
よろしくね、マンゴー
No.
ダメ
By myself.
自分でさ
Have the mango opened.
マンゴー開いてもらう
Open your legs.
足開いて
It turned out to be amazing.
すごいことになったね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
嫌だよ
looks delicious.
美味しそう
I don't like it.
嫌だね
amazing.
すごい
I don't like it.
嫌だ